[
    {
        "created_utc": 1574970087.0,
        "title": "[Orsborn] DeMar on clearing his Instagram account: \"I don’t even like social media, honestly. I’m not a big fan of social media, never been. To this day I always wish I had played in the 90s so I wouldn’t deal with social media. I just let people talk. Me, personally, I hate it.\"",
        "body": "> DeMar on clearing his Instagram account: \"I don’t even like social media, honestly. I’m not a big fan of social media, never been. To this day I always wish I had played in the 90s so I wouldn’t deal with social media. I just let people talk. Me, personally, I hate it.\" #Spurs\n\n\n\n[Source: Tom Orsborn](https://twitter.com/tom_orsborn/status/1199911853679370241)",
        "score": 11136,
        "distinguished": null,
        "title_sentiment": 4.0,
        "body_sentiment": 4.0,
        "title_entities": [
            {
                "PERSON": "DeMar"
            },
            {
                "GPE": "Instagram"
            },
            {
                "DATE": "this day"
            },
            {
                "DATE": "90s"
            }
        ],
        "body_entities": [
            {
                "PERSON": "DeMar"
            },
            {
                "GPE": "Instagram"
            },
            {
                "DATE": "this day"
            },
            {
                "DATE": "90s"
            },
            {
                "MONEY": "Spurs"
            },
            {
                "PERSON": "Tom Orsborn](https://twitter.com/tom_orsborn/status/1199911853679370241"
            }
        ]
    },
    [
        {
            "created_utc": 1574971985.0,
            "body": "He should delete it. Nothing wrong with that",
            "score": 2455,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970173.0,
            "body": "DeMar wishes he would play in the 90s for another reason as well.",
            "score": 5163,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "90s"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970240.0,
            "body": "I couldn’t agree more. Most forms of social media are cancer.",
            "score": 1335,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574971746.0,
            "body": "Look at ya'll roasting Derozan in here. No wonder he hates social media. I hate when one of the nicest guys in the league, the first to open up publicly about his depression is the most bullied because he doesn't shoot 3s but wait-- he still gets 20-30 pts every game.",
            "score": 3439,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -10.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Derozan"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "one"
                },
                {
                    "ORDINAL": "first"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "3s"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "20-30"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574973953.0,
            "body": "I heard on the radio today that DeMar was at a fast food restaurant drive thru when he got the news and he just kind of chilled in his car in the parking lot for a few hours reflecting. Is this true?",
            "score": 399,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "today"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                },
                {
                    "TIME": "a few hours"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574981518.0,
            "body": "Demar gets too much hate he’s dope",
            "score": 254,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Demar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574982154.0,
            "body": "This whole thread is why he hates social media",
            "score": 183,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970202.0,
            "body": "He’d be a perfect players for the 90s",
            "score": 244,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "90s"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574982794.0,
            "body": "I'm the same way, honestly.\n\nThe worst is, you realize there are people who will judge you based off it, and come to conclusions about your essential character based off your instagram.  As if there's no way you could be someone that couldn't be summed up by instagram or selfies or 'capturing' your life moments there.  Or that you just flat-out don't care and make no effort to 'look good' for social media.\n\nAnybody who uses tinder or dating apps knows it's extremely common to have someone ask for your instagram.   And then (this has happened multiple times) unmatch you or stop communication when they check out your page.",
            "score": 45,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574978739.0,
            "body": "Respect! 🤜🤛",
            "score": 28,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574978288.0,
            "body": "of course r/nba doesn't care. they're just gonna continue bullying players.  we've got some really dumb nephews on the internet. no wonder he doesn't like social media.",
            "score": 266,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574979495.0,
            "body": "Instagram and Twitter can be super unhealthy for ones mental health so I do not blame him in the least for getting off those platforms.",
            "score": 34,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Instagram"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Twitter"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574971643.0,
            "body": "if he hates it so much he should just go full kawhi. may not be possible basketball-wise but he can delete all his social media easily",
            "score": 97,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574971914.0,
            "body": "I am DeMar",
            "score": 70,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574974245.0,
            "body": "He clears his social like 2 times a year why is this news",
            "score": 44,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "2"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574991531.0,
            "body": "Instagram fools people into thinking everyone lives an exciting, adventurous, happy life when they only get a very small portion of the bigger picture.  I know a beautiful girl who has thousands of followers on instagram and if you looked soley at her social media profiles you would think she were living the most glamarous and happy life ever.  In reality she barely survived a severe bout with depression and still has problems in her recovery.  Shes a completely normal person with really serious demons and real world problems and you would never know it by looking at her social media profile.  Point is, this shit is a fun house mirror of reality and it can and has fucked with so many peoples minds by having them take it too seriously.",
            "score": 10,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Instagram"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "thousands"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Point"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574976941.0,
            "body": "I deleted all of my social media the day I graduated high school. I feel like it’s become even worse since then now that the new generation has latched onto it",
            "score": 22,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "the day"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574978643.0,
            "body": "A bit sad he deleted his posts there, I liked his stuff, he had some Raptors stuff too and it was good memories. Miss him on our team but happy for our continued success.",
            "score": 5,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 6.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574977121.0,
            "body": "I avoid social media too. Which is ironic considering I work for a major social media company haha.",
            "score": 16,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574981118.0,
            "body": "In my honest opinion, DeMar and Kawhi would probably be good friends. They both hate the media, they would rather NOT have social media and they're big fans of the midrange. It just sucks that they were traded for one another and probably wouldn't be teammates.",
            "score": 15,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970196.0,
            "body": "If Demar played in the 90s, he’d be a MVP candidate",
            "score": 98,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Demar"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "the 90s"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "MVP"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970390.0,
            "body": "There's a reason why Bron shuts off all his social media come playoff time.",
            "score": 14,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Bron"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574991363.0,
            "body": "KD could learn a thing or two from this man",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "KD"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "two"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574995066.0,
            "body": ">**I always wish I had played in the 90s**\n\nCan someone please link the legendary photoshop of the Raptors as if they played in the 80s",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "90s"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "80s"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575005874.0,
            "body": "Love his take on social media. It’s taken over our lives. I’ll always be a fan of his. Doesn’t need to be posting updates for everyone to know. Enjoy life for yourself not for others.",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 8.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574975532.0,
            "body": "DeMar is my spirit animal.",
            "score": 5,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574971043.0,
            "body": "Yeah that definitely the only reason DeMar wants to play in the 90s",
            "score": 10,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "the 90s"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574993264.0,
            "body": "I think that post trade DeMar just lacks certain kind of aggression from his earlier years in the league. I haven't followed his stats to back up the opinion but I feel his posture isn't nowhere near the posture of a bonafide superstar in the league. If he could borrow some of the mentality from Westbrook he'd really step up to the role of the team leader. And while I don't think he'd defensively be near the likes of Kawhi and PG, I still think he has figuring out to do into how to lead a team with the burden of being the best player on the team and a go-to guy to win. There are players in the league who openly hate social media (Kawhi, Jokic) yet they ball out every night and they thrive under pressure in the playoffs.",
            "score": 4,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "DeMar"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "his earlier years"
                },
                {
                    "WORK_OF_ART": "Westbrook"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Jokic"
                },
                {
                    "TIME": "every night"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574981923.0,
            "body": "It's pretty sad that this is even a question. Hawking social media for stories is about as low as it gets.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574992085.0,
            "body": "Unpopular popular opinion",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574992758.0,
            "body": "dude it sucks when everyone expects you to have one and look at you wierd when you tell them you dont.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574994319.0,
            "body": "Man so much simpler without social media",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574994905.0,
            "body": "Why is this even a story?  Who cares lol",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 5.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574997135.0,
            "body": "You really gotta feel for DeMar. Watching the raps win the championship must have been a bittersweet experience for him.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574997347.0,
            "body": "he should delete it, havent had it for i think 3 year now, never looked back.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "3 year"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574997644.0,
            "body": "Feel ya bruh.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574997959.0,
            "body": "Social media is a cancer. Good for you for recognizing it Demar",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Demar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574999208.0,
            "body": "The only social media I use is Twitter and that's mainly to keep up to date with sports and the world in general. I've had Facebook and Instagram and find it toxic.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Twitter"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Facebook"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Instagram"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575000100.0,
            "body": "I actually made a Twitter recently and only use to see discussions on the stuff I like same with instagram. I have social media and don’t post on any of the shit. I’m a recluse but fck social media when I 1st got it I used to fake it on Instagram then thought about why am I doing this shit? Now I go on Instagram to see sneakers and thots twerk 👀",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -9.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Twitter"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Instagram"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Instagram"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575001538.0,
            "body": "Demar's playstyle would be perfect in the 90s and early 00s",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Demar"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "the 90s"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "early 00s"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575006360.0,
            "body": "I get it",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575026503.0,
            "body": "If he played even earlier than the 90s, before the 3pt line was started, he would be legendary.\n\nOld school dude and game.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "earlier than the 90s"
                },
                {
                    "ORDINAL": "3pt"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970286.0,
            "body": "Completely agree with ya!",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574976349.0,
            "body": "I was born in the wrong generation /s\n\nBut fr I get what he's saying.",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575008477.0,
            "body": "I don’t think there is a sane person alive that likes social media, or thinks it is healthy",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 5.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575005986.0,
            "body": "Then don't use it?  \nI don't understand why some people make it sound like social media is forced upon you.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574975024.0,
            "body": "Sounds like somebody's been spending time with Duncan.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Duncan"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574993086.0,
            "body": "“I don’t even like social media.”.... continues to be on social media",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970310.0,
            "body": "He wished he played in the 90’s because he knows his game don’t translate to today",
            "score": -1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "90"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "today"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574976388.0,
            "body": "Welcome to the end of the decade, where deleting a picture will cause controversy😅",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "the end of the decade"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574977917.0,
            "body": "Me and Demar think the same.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Demar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574981734.0,
            "body": "Traded the next day",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "the next day"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574982274.0,
            "body": "Yah I also wish I played in the 90's.  For the Bulls...",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "90"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574983147.0,
            "body": "Does he have to have an account?",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574984557.0,
            "body": "It's actually a real shame if this isn't ok for players to do.  They have a legitimate right to privacy.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574985503.0,
            "body": "relatable",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574985869.0,
            "body": "I'm with you, DeMar.  I hate social media and do not have any of those types of accounts.  99% is all noise.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                },
                {
                    "PERCENT": "99%"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574986254.0,
            "body": "he needs to be like kawhi \"whats social media\"",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574986344.0,
            "body": "Excellent role model",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574986561.0,
            "body": "Can't agree more. I remember when Facebook came out and I was able to get in because I was in college and it was limited. Then it opened up to more people and I remember the immediate decline. Social media started becoming festering pool of societies worst concentrated in one place. Do you really think DeMar is wrong here? Or is it just easier to join in and roast him?",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Facebook"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "one"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574987005.0,
            "body": "Me when it comes to dating and social media lmao",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574987989.0,
            "body": "Although I think he may be covering here, I agree wholeheartedly. I've deleted so many of my social media accounts and every time it feels good and improves my life.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 6.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574988601.0,
            "body": "Imagine if Kyrie said this",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Kyrie"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989021.0,
            "body": "Honestly I just couldn’t get too hooked on that shit though I use Instagram to look at hot girls. But even then it does affect your confidence fmo\nAnd really do feel like it has issues. I love House of highlights and even barstool sports videos but you sometimes see people your age posts and sometimes you feel that regret if you see them posting about their frat life or this and that. But for me as I am older and do other things, those things aren’t everything and I think Instagram really does paint some misconceptions about life and also affect people’s confidence. Same time I look at these hot fitness girls on Instagram and some of them are shitty as fuck and obnoxious. Like this one girl is hot but one time she posted some snap story About how she ghosted some dude on a date cause she didn’t like him or some Bs. Thing was she could’ve done that and kept it private but she posted it. Like for me instagram is a big part of why people today get sensostive about shot and can’t act rationally at times.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Instagram"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "\n"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "House"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Instagram"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Instagram"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "one"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Bs"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "today"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989031.0,
            "body": "Amen. The whole “influencers” generation is terrible",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989164.0,
            "body": "All you assholes think your opinions matter. At the end of the day, DeMar is eating grapes off a vine in Beverly Hills while you’re reorganizing your bosses files.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "the end of the day"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Beverly Hills"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989179.0,
            "body": "This is one of the few times I've been able to relate to an NBA player on a personal level. I am in agreement, 100%. Social media, in my opinion, is leading the decay in civility, empathy, and overall mental soundness in people. Causes most of the division, fear-mongering, and distrust you see today in your everyday lives.\n\nIt's sad and I fear it will only get worse until we reach a critical level where people actually begin to move away from it. I personally don't think it will ever happen, but we'll see if it does.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -10.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "one"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "NBA"
                },
                {
                    "PERCENT": "100%"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "today"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989655.0,
            "body": "Agreed. Fuck SNS",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989692.0,
            "body": "He plays in the 90s but he has to trade with someone and let him play in this decade:\n\nI trade DeMar for Sabonis",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "the 90s"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "this decade"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "DeMar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574990328.0,
            "body": "The only social media I use and am addicted to Reddit. \n\nI rarely ever tweet or post on Instagram or Facebook. I'm always considering deleting my accounts as well",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Reddit"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Instagram"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Facebook"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574990333.0,
            "body": "same i wish i lived in the 90's.\n\nthen only thing i like from today is the movies games anime and some music all the rest is trash",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "today"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574991104.0,
            "body": "Social media is a fad",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574991224.0,
            "body": "He’s not alone.. more and more people are realizing how stupid it is.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574991806.0,
            "body": "Its so easy to get caught up in people complementing and cheering for you. Then boom, one misuderstood poorly depicted media story and you get 15000 comments crapping on you, after the illusion of support has set in. It sounds difficult tbh. Definitely a first world problem but it's still real.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "one"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "15000"
                },
                {
                    "ORDINAL": "first"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574992349.0,
            "body": "Good for him.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574992427.0,
            "body": "He gone man",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574992649.0,
            "body": "I feel you DeDe. I haven’t been posted on any social media(besides reddit) in like 3 years.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeDe"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "like 3 years"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574992721.0,
            "body": "Born in the wrong generation- filthy frank",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574993206.0,
            "body": "This is the first step of turning into Kawhi. \n\nNext step: play defense",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORDINAL": "first"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574993724.0,
            "body": "Shame him for not wanting to see what I'm eating for breakfast. ^^it's ^^pancake ^^mix ^^with ^^sugar ^^and ^^milk ^^pretending ^^as ^^syrup",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574994014.0,
            "body": "DeMar's game would also fit the 90s better",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "90s"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574994376.0,
            "body": "Demar and Vince carter on the raptors oof",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Demar"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Vince"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574994481.0,
            "body": "Go full Kawhi!!!",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574994493.0,
            "body": "DeMar is a solid player and an amazing person. People need to stop giving this guy so much slack. Toronto adores him and would never say anything bad about him. Why can’t everyone else do the same. Fuck people",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "DeMar"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Toronto"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574994953.0,
            "body": "Deep down he cared, but social media been rough on him.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574995149.0,
            "body": "He would probably have been appreciated more as a player in the 90s too.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "90s"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574995744.0,
            "body": "Good .  just Cut out the nice and focus on your game. Cant let online trolls get to your head unlike kd",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 5.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Cut"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574996057.0,
            "body": "Demar was lookin at the gram and he dont even like likes",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Demar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574996154.0,
            "body": "That's a lie.  He has always used social media to push his brand or image during his time in Toronto.  I just think he can't handle social media when his play comes into question.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Toronto"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574997649.0,
            "body": "What's going on with him?",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574998590.0,
            "body": "get off his lawn.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574999285.0,
            "body": "But what does he think of social media?",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574999446.0,
            "body": "Sounds like a copy pasta",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574999690.0,
            "body": "On the gram and I don't even like likes",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574999774.0,
            "body": "Lol DeMar would have dominated the 90s and 2000s. \n\nHe's one of those players stuck in the wrong era",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Lol DeMar"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "the 90s and 2000s"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "one"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574999823.0,
            "body": "I feel like most people don't realize how hard it is to do this.  Do you know how much sponsors try to get on your social medias,  and that pressure on top of all this publicity it gets.   We really need to just let people live.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575001081.0,
            "body": "Do people consider Reddit social media? And the 90's probably wasn't all that good since there was a lot of tabloids, and there was almost no way to publicly defend yourself without getting on tv or radio.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Reddit"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575001306.0,
            "body": "Good for him!",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575001455.0,
            "body": "What do Spurs fans really think about Derozan? Just curious.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Spurs"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Derozan"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575002600.0,
            "body": "He mad cuz he aint with Raptors anymore",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575002735.0,
            "body": "Same Demar.\n\nIf I ever get any semblance of money I'm deleting all my social media, which is just IG now anyway.. And reddit I guess, but that's fairly different.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Demar"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "IG"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575002777.0,
            "body": "Thank god, please make this a trend so by the time my son hits school it’s somehow not a thing anymore....",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575002929.0,
            "body": "i love this. bravo. takes a lot to break the cycle",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575003318.0,
            "body": "Some days I’ve felt that my mental health took a nosedive the day I created a Facebook account 10 years ago. It can be real motherfucker.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -5.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "Some days"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Facebook"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "10 years ago"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575008054.0,
            "body": "If there's one thing people who don't like social media like doing, it's telling you that they don't like social media",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 6.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "one"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575023627.0,
            "body": "Real One.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "One"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575024935.0,
            "body": "Dude’s gameplay is from 90’s and now his mentality is from 90’s as well lmao",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "90"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "90"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575026936.0,
            "body": "But how does he feel about social media?",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575028597.0,
            "body": "I’m the same dude, no Facebook or Instagram. Just reddit and messenger app.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Facebook"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Instagram"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575028768.0,
            "body": "DeMar should delay Instagram and join Reddit",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Instagram"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Reddit"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575028864.0,
            "body": "i still dont have twitter and instagram. the only social media account i had were from friendster and facebook, and the only active left is this reddit account",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575030915.0,
            "body": "I mean, I feel him but it's not like he's obligated to have any social media presence. Plenty of other athletes don't.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575032280.0,
            "body": "DeMar on clearing his Instagram account: \"I don’t even like social media, honestly. I’m not a big fan of social media, never been. To this day I always wish I had played in the 90s so I wouldn’t deal with social media. I just let people talk. Me, personally, I hate it.\" #Spurs",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Instagram"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "this day"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "90s"
                },
                {
                    "MONEY": "Spurs"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575032335.0,
            "body": "Your skill set wishes you played in the 90’s as well. It’s not a knock on Derozan Bc I think he can ball, but he’s one of the few dominate mid range shooters left that can’t really shoot 3’s.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "90"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Derozan Bc"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "one"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "3"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575033747.0,
            "body": "Took the words right out of my mouth, Demar.\n\n*Keeps scrolling reddit*",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Demar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575035733.0,
            "body": "I haven't had any form of social media in about 2 years.  Life has been significantly better because of it.  I feel like a human instead of an endlessly scrolling zombie",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "about 2 years"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575039182.0,
            "body": "What if we all did this.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575039201.0,
            "body": "Sounds like me lol I hate ig Facebook and Twitter",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Facebook"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Twitter"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575040388.0,
            "body": "Good for him. Social media is worthless.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575040392.0,
            "body": "I think it’s crazy that he had to make a public statement about this",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575040987.0,
            "body": "I recommend everyone deletes social media. It's crazy how younger generation who grew up with it thinks it's impossible to live without, yet if they just got rid of it they'd see how amazing it is. I've been off facebook and instagram for 3 or 4 years now and it's I don't miss it at all.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "3 or 4 years"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575042794.0,
            "body": "What a great mindset. This Twitter, Facebook, instacrap and Snapchat garbage seems more of job/hassle then actually communicating with friends. Real men stay away from that nonsense",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Twitter"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Facebook"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575050340.0,
            "body": "r/nba in shambles",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574986515.0,
            "body": "Kawhi just doesn't do it and he gets by fine",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574985998.0,
            "body": "So many backhanded compliments in this thread, \"hE'd Be tHe PeRfeCt 90s PLayER\"",
            "score": 0,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 5.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "90s"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970177.0,
            "body": "Same.",
            "score": -2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574974306.0,
            "body": "i mean... its still a choice to use it. think kawhi gives a shit about anything related to online social media?",
            "score": -1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970258.0,
            "body": "Derozan would be MJ in the 90s",
            "score": -17,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Derozan"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "MJ"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "the 90s"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989217.0,
            "body": "Thats why you hire a social media manager buddy",
            "score": 0,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574996560.0,
            "body": "No one is making you be on social media.",
            "score": 0,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574998763.0,
            "body": "This is total bullshit. He used to be huge on social media before he came out with his mental struggles.",
            "score": 0,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -5.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575003950.0,
            "body": "Hes a multi-millionaire. Why can't he just find someone to run his social media for him?",
            "score": 0,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574978638.0,
            "body": "So basically he doesnt like three point shots.",
            "score": -9,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "three"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574979661.0,
            "body": "BS\n\n\nYou know who really hates social media? Guys like Kawhi who don’t even have social media counts \n\n\nDemar has a Twitter, insta, Snapchat, etc",
            "score": -6,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Twitter"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574973534.0,
            "body": "DeMar, you have a choice to not have any social media. You know that right?",
            "score": -6,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574976628.0,
            "body": "yeah but you wouldnt have made as much money in the 90s. Honestly he could just decide to shut it all off and not have to look at it, or better yet, hire someone to do the PR stuff for you, they will manage all your profiles and brand endorsements and other PR stuff, and you can be mostly isolated from that chap by just insulating yourself with ppl..",
            "score": -1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "90s"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574987424.0,
            "body": "Well if Demar played in the 90s he would have been Michael Jordan\n\n/s",
            "score": -1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Demar"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "the 90s"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Michael Jordan"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575013904.0,
            "body": "If he played in the 90s, he'll be the G.O.A.T.",
            "score": -1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "the 90s"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "G.O.A.T."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575032977.0,
            "body": "I wish Demar shot 3’a as good as he shoots ropes!",
            "score": -1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Demar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970478.0,
            "body": ">Me, personally, I hate it. #Spurs\n\nDeMar to Toronto confirmed",
            "score": -11,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "MONEY": "Spurs"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Toronto"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574986475.0,
            "body": "Then don't use it?",
            "score": -5,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574987484.0,
            "body": "Then delete it.  But he won't.",
            "score": -6,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574987360.0,
            "body": "He plays in San Antonio\n\nPeople dont even remember he exists\n\nHe needs this PR",
            "score": -2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "San Antonio"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989087.0,
            "body": "Damn if only the spurs can clear him that easy",
            "score": -2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574986823.0,
            "body": "DeMar wishes he played in the 90s because of how he plays don’t kid",
            "score": -2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "90s"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970723.0,
            "body": "Maybe he'll shoot more threes in the 90's",
            "score": -11,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "90"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970522.0,
            "body": "Jordan is lucky he played in the 90s or he would be a scrub in today’s game",
            "score": -24,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Jordan"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "90s"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "today"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989683.0,
            "body": "Fuckin Jews",
            "score": -6,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Fuckin Jews"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574981995.0,
            "body": "He should delete his accounts then.",
            "score": -7,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574982248.0,
            "body": "[deleted]",
            "score": -15,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574988402.0,
            "body": "For real. Kawhi doesn't have social media and he seems to be doing ok.",
            "score": 982,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989741.0,
            "body": "Could you imagine if every athlete deleted their social media? Sports shows would actually have to talk about sports again...",
            "score": 285,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574987782.0,
            "body": "He wipes it every year",
            "score": 14,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574983429.0,
            "body": "or just get a PR manager",
            "score": 126,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574992076.0,
            "body": "He wipes it all clean every few months",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "every few months"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574995520.0,
            "body": "The amount of toxic reactions you receive for deleting social media nowadays is absolutely crazy. I deleted my Facebook 2 years back and friends/family were straight up mean to me about it.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "2 years"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575020410.0,
            "body": "Yeah, if he hates it...delete it.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574992244.0,
            "body": "probably has to keep it for endorsements",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575046120.0,
            "body": "Was he not allowed to?",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989504.0,
            "body": "Seriously. Stop bitching, the answer is the delete button",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574971509.0,
            "body": "DeMar lives in the past for sure. The way he plays and the way he operates proves that. He’s a 90s kid",
            "score": 2222,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "90s"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574987307.0,
            "body": "Don't think he wants to be clotheslined by Karl Malone or Greg Ostertag",
            "score": 44,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Karl Malone"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Greg Ostertag"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574983720.0,
            "body": "Because of his midrange dominant game? Or am I missing an obvious joke here",
            "score": 179,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574987261.0,
            "body": "So he could watch Kenan and Kel?",
            "score": 33,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Kenan"
                },
                {
                    "NORP": "Kel"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970299.0,
            "body": "Less nobodies trying to tell you how to hoop and a higher % of fans actually watching the games\n\nEDIT: 2nd point is prolly bs (though I legit believe a lot of ppl here don't watch shit) but at least they didn't have a platform to spout dumb shit for the world to see",
            "score": 253,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -11.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORDINAL": "2nd"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574985216.0,
            "body": "This comment is so ironic in contrast to what he said, like seriously sometimes reddit has absolutely no self-awareness.",
            "score": 18,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574985054.0,
            "body": "Cause he hates 3 pointers?",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "3"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574983652.0,
            "body": "He’d still be a borderline allstar",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989581.0,
            "body": "[deleted]",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575043599.0,
            "body": "His bank account doesn't wish he played in the 90s.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "the 90s"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574980821.0,
            "body": "Have an upvote good sir.",
            "score": -7,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970453.0,
            "body": "instagram is one of the worst communities i have ever come across",
            "score": 549,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574972621.0,
            "body": "Every comment is 🤡🤡🤡",
            "score": 32,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970355.0,
            "body": "Reddit is social media",
            "score": 128,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Reddit"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970768.0,
            "body": "Social media is pretty cancer if you’re always on it. I use twitter but don’t turn on notifications. Going on it occasionally is the key.",
            "score": 30,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574975585.0,
            "body": "I disagree. You just gotta work on your filter. Theyre fun to enjoy when you kno how to block out the trash",
            "score": 7,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574988649.0,
            "body": "Instagram is cancer, but Twitter is cancer and aids.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Instagram"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Twitter"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574990495.0,
            "body": "i wish i never installed snapchat, i hate that i feel almost obligated to snap when something happens when i eat when i travel etc.. please take me back to before i installed it",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575017722.0,
            "body": "I agree people post worthless stuff on there all the time.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575023188.0,
            "body": "What are you doing here then?",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575041026.0,
            "body": "Which social media platform do you think isn’t cancer?",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575046269.0,
            "body": "social media only propels the wealthy or those who have no aspirations to pursue a career with integrity. There are some people that take it serious or do things for fun or hobbies\n\nIf I had money, I'd honestly stay on social media all day looking up random hoes to smash and locking up endorsements deals with all these different companies(somehow Cadri B is a Pepsi spokesperson now, how Sway?)",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 7.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "all day"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Cadri"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Pepsi"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Sway"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574973484.0,
            "body": "His game was so fun to watch too, I miss watching him slither his way to the rim every night, yes winning is fun too but we did a lot of that when he was here too, it just never transferred to the playoffs. I miss the guy in TO, I hope he comes back to us in the tail end of his career",
            "score": 931,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 11.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "TIME": "every night"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574983968.0,
            "body": "The internet is awful. It's funny though, the majority of these people would not even be able to handle any of the shit they spew out if it was directed at them. \n\nWe all need a little more empathy. Imagine a bunch of cheeto fingered assholes constantly tweeting at you that you're the worst sandwich artist in the history of subway.\n\nIt's like that Seinfeld episode. If a comedian came and heckled you at your job, you'd probably run out of the building and get your pinky toe severed by a taxi.",
            "score": 105,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "NORP": "Seinfeld"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574985634.0,
            "body": "It's like people decided DeMar should be a superstar, then got mad at him when he wasn't.",
            "score": 25,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574973716.0,
            "body": "He’s a huge defensive liability, but he’s a nice guy. I think him being with a coach that emphasizes priorities other than basketball is good for him, too.",
            "score": 171,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 7.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574995405.0,
            "body": "When Lou Will scores 20 its all love when Demar does it hes somehow still hurting the team",
            "score": 8,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Lou Will"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "20"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Demar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574973133.0,
            "body": "Fans have every right to criticize players, they exist for our entertainment /s",
            "score": 85,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574990777.0,
            "body": "Felt this way for a while now, thanks for saying it.",
            "score": 4,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574985871.0,
            "body": "Facts.",
            "score": 5,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574995020.0,
            "body": "I fucking hate this subreddit.",
            "score": 7,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -7.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574992826.0,
            "body": "he's also a pretty efficient scorer. 588 ts% for this year is not bad\n\nlove u deebo",
            "score": 4,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "this year"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574993490.0,
            "body": "You posted “DeMar wipes IG” on the spurs sub... You’re part of the problem.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574973849.0,
            "body": "What does nice have to do with anything? Are people making fun of his children? His looks? \n\nAre bball fans not allowed to talk bball anymore?",
            "score": -4,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 7.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575009630.0,
            "body": "Him opening up about his depression is irrelevant",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574985861.0,
            "body": "Are you not allowed to criticize people ?",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574993573.0,
            "body": "Lmao I've never seen him be roasted here. Except from tiny people. Never been a legit thread or nothing. Keep victimizing the man though.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574977815.0,
            "body": "y’all*",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574990587.0,
            "body": "If you think derozan is one of the most bullied then you’re living in Lala land",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Lala"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574983655.0,
            "body": "Ah yes, the great metric \"points per game\" being used to measure a players value.",
            "score": -1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574983993.0,
            "body": "It's fine that DeMar hates and avoids social media.\n\nThat doesn't mean people shouldn't be free to roast people they dislike.\n\nYou know what's sad? We are more fixated on his haters than his supporters.",
            "score": -2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -7.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574986880.0,
            "body": "He’s bullied because he’s not that good",
            "score": 0,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574980564.0,
            "body": "are people not allowed to criticize players? lol, should we just think every player is equally good? DD isn't even the most bullied player in the NBA.",
            "score": -6,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "DD"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "NBA"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574983177.0,
            "body": "Normal people think and reflect.",
            "score": 130,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574982953.0,
            "body": "It was a jack in the box if you must know",
            "score": 168,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574975647.0,
            "body": "yes",
            "score": 85,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574978476.0,
            "body": "News?",
            "score": 49,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989690.0,
            "body": "Bruh you made me panic and think that DeMar got traded again",
            "score": 29,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Bruh"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574979692.0,
            "body": "Idk it's not mention on his Twitter so probably not.",
            "score": 8,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574987018.0,
            "body": "What news? When he was traded?",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574990219.0,
            "body": "For real. I never understood why guys like him and Curry get hate.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Curry"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575003545.0,
            "body": "Which comments in particular? There are like two comments joking how he'd rather be in the 90's also because his play is more oriented to that, and then a ton of comments like yours preemptively acting like this thread is bullying him.",
            "score": 4,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "two"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "90"
                },
                {
                    "QUANTITY": "a ton"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574983233.0,
            "body": "Are we just ignoring that he'd still get burned on defense in the 90s as well?",
            "score": -29,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "90s"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574987056.0,
            "body": "Gross culture.",
            "score": 16,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575047895.0,
            "body": "so I used to be in class with this girl, we had known each other briefly and took the same class so we could share the book, since I could borrow it for free.\n\nMy friend was also in the class, and we noticed she would randomly stare at us. Turns out she was memorizing our seats and counting out names on the attendance sheet to see where we signed to figure out his name. She eventually found his name(cause she never talked to him) and stalked his IG profile, and when he tried to comment on her page, she locked her account and wouldnt accept his request\n\nSo fast forward, we start catching feelings, but this incident has to be addressed, so I indirectly call her IG handle out. She tries to deflect and pin the issue on me. I do it again a second time to see if she catches on to how I know, she pulls up my full name from work and tries to search me on facebook(didnt work cause I have a nickname in my profile name, but havent used it in over 8 years)\n\nMy boss is cool with me and her, she knows the drama, I know they talked, my boss basically tells me that her feelings are hurt and I should apologize - I still havent apologized to this day",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "IG"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "IG"
                },
                {
                    "ORDINAL": "second"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "over 8 years"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "this day"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574988649.0,
            "body": "I've never been a part of a sub that spews as much hatred as this does. Most comments are unbelieavebly ignorant and agressive to the players and god help you if you go against the current circlejerk",
            "score": 51,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574992285.0,
            "body": "If Luka, Giannis or Curry said this everyone would feel sorry for him",
            "score": 14,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Luka"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Giannis"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Curry"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575001982.0,
            "body": "Can you explain how r/NBA has supposedly bullied DeMar DeRozan? There are some players that I understand, but DeMar I dunno.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "NBA"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar DeRozan"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574984307.0,
            "body": "Pretty sure Demar doesn't go on reddit or give a fuck about what we have to say on here. He is probably talking about twitter and instagram.",
            "score": -8,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Demar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575021006.0,
            "body": "What is a nephew",
            "score": 0,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574991258.0,
            "body": "Instagram especially can make you feel like everyone else is living life to the fullest and you arent doing enough when its all based off a completely distorted version of reality.",
            "score": 10,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575036119.0,
            "body": "Anytime I hear about someone not being on any social media I automatically assume they are a mentally healthy person who has their shit together.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574981089.0,
            "body": "Maybe could. I don't use social media outside here but I keep running into reasons to keep accounts open. You could just a easily live without a cell phone.",
            "score": 17,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574983338.0,
            "body": "He only hates it because it's critical of him. He'd be way more on board if his game matched that of Kawhi and had the correlating praise.",
            "score": -20,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574986338.0,
            "body": "Hey",
            "score": 14,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574982427.0,
            "body": "Because the spurs suck worse than last year",
            "score": 57,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -6.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "last year"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575001133.0,
            "body": "Escape from reality has existed for hundreds of years, it’s just changed, in terms of the mediums we use.",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "hundreds of years"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575004397.0,
            "body": "Yeah I feel that too. Some of the instagram girls on social media seem nice or whaetever but sometimes I feel like they are hiding things and could be shitty in real life. It's just not everything like people makeit out to be.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575036215.0,
            "body": "Instagram is basically just a person's highlight reel.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Instagram"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574990578.0,
            "body": "Thank God social media wasn't around when I was in high school.",
            "score": 11,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989735.0,
            "body": "I changed careers because I realised that social media marketing became the norm and I couldn't handle pretending to be down with something I hated. Hang in there.",
            "score": 10,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574988726.0,
            "body": "You probably know more than most people how bad it can be tho",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574992691.0,
            "body": "R/nobodyAsked",
            "score": -2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989471.0,
            "body": "who’s to say they aren’t friends cause they aren’t on the same team lol?",
            "score": 4,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574988906.0,
            "body": "DeMar doesn't hate the media",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970334.0,
            "body": "Hell to the no especially with MJ dominating",
            "score": 210,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -5.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "MJ"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574974694.0,
            "body": "Tf lol, no he wouldn't. His playstyle would be more accepted but he's not even that good at hitting midrange shots. He'd be like a B tier All-Star. Keep in mind the 90's MVP were Barkley, Hakeem, Jordan, Robinson, & Malone...DeMar doesn't hold a candle to those guys.",
            "score": 33,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 8.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "90"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "MVP"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Barkley"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Hakeem"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Jordan"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Robinson"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "& Malone"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574972337.0,
            "body": "Nah he'd be putting up similar summers but in a losing team. Most offenses still went through big men and big men led teams were more successful. MJ, Drexler and Miller were just exceptions. And even Miller was only just an all star.",
            "score": 20,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Nah"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Drexler"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Miller"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Miller"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574971003.0,
            "body": "lol",
            "score": 14,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970933.0,
            "body": "No he wouldn't. He'd be Jerry Stackhouse or Latrell Spreewell tier.",
            "score": 68,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Jerry Stackhouse"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Latrell Spreewell"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574977522.0,
            "body": "This is a bad take. I don’t even think you believe it, you were just doing it for the likes and you feel a little bad about what he is saying",
            "score": 6,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574971065.0,
            "body": "I doubt it.  He isn't even elite from mid range.  Not sure why so many people say he is.",
            "score": 44,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574970470.0,
            "body": "Because there would be no information right",
            "score": 6,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574978603.0,
            "body": "Dunno why people are acting like you said he'd be MVP, unless you post before editing said MVP not MVP candidate.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "MVP"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "MVP"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "MVP"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574989607.0,
            "body": "Yeah, but he's also probably one of the most active NBA players on social media during all other times. Too active if you ask me.",
            "score": 19,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "one"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "NBA"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575023865.0,
            "body": "Emphasis on the sane..... There's so many who live and die by social media... Its sad",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -5.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575050834.0,
            "body": "Im assuming you are not a person who might be discussed at any given time on national television because of your job",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574992421.0,
            "body": "They are all horrible for being an echo chamber",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575038426.0,
            "body": "\"giving slack\" is a positive thing. I think you mean \"giving flack\"?",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575039477.0,
            "body": "On insta, people show off their ass.\n\nOn Reddit, people show off their opinions",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Reddit"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574987981.0,
            "body": "Exactly.  And he got booed by Spurs fans but didn't tell us his feelings like Kyrie",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Spurs"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Kyrie"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574975533.0,
            "body": "I don’t understand why ppl think Kawhi is weird for not having social media, but all these players that complain about how much they hate social media while also being on social media is even more weird to me.",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -9.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574971403.0,
            "body": "I feel like MJ would be MJ in the 90s",
            "score": 24,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "MJ"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "MJ"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "the 90s"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1574973718.0,
            "body": "Lmao",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": []
        },
        {
