[
    {
        "created_utc": 1575052339.0,
        "title": "[Wolstat] Pascal Siakam hit one three-pointer as a rookie, 29 as a sophomore. Nailed five last night. Now hitting 2.5 a game at 39% accuracy. He steps back with ease. Absolute nightmare to defend. What a unique story.",
        "body": "Siakam's growth from bad role player, good role player, all star level to now playing mvp caliber ball has been a magical experience for Raptor fans following him throughout the journey. \n\nHas there even been a player who improved his shooting ability significantly EVERY single year? Attempts and percentage alike. I personally thought he peaked last year on 2.7 attempts a game (37%) from a PJ Tucker esque corner shooting only. However, he came this year guns blazing! Pulling up, doing step backs and shooting with defenders draped all over him. All from the top of key which he barely shot from last year. \n\nHis shooting numbers:\n(Attempts from 3)\n\n0.1 on .143%\n\n1.6 on .220%\n\n2.7 on .369%\n\n6.3 on .393%\n\n\n\nTweet source: https://twitter.com/WolstatSun/status/1200097424364261376?s=19",
        "score": 6628,
        "distinguished": null,
        "title_sentiment": 2.0,
        "body_sentiment": 11.0,
        "title_entities": [
            {
                "PERSON": "Wolstat"
            },
            {
                "PERSON": "Pascal Siakam"
            },
            {
                "CARDINAL": "one"
            },
            {
                "CARDINAL": "three"
            },
            {
                "CARDINAL": "29"
            },
            {
                "TIME": "five last night"
            },
            {
                "CARDINAL": "2.5"
            },
            {
                "PERCENT": "39%"
            }
        ],
        "body_entities": [
            {
                "ORG": "Siakam"
            },
            {
                "DATE": "EVERY single year"
            },
            {
                "GPE": "Attempts"
            },
            {
                "DATE": "last year"
            },
            {
                "CARDINAL": "2.7"
            },
            {
                "PERCENT": "37%"
            },
            {
                "ORG": "PJ Tucker"
            },
            {
                "DATE": "this year"
            },
            {
                "DATE": "last year"
            },
            {
                "GPE": "\n"
            },
            {
                "CARDINAL": "3"
            },
            {
                "CARDINAL": "0.1"
            },
            {
                "CARDINAL": "1.6"
            },
            {
                "PERCENT": ".220%"
            },
            {
                "CARDINAL": "2.7"
            },
            {
                "PERCENT": ".369%"
            },
            {
                "PRODUCT": "6.3"
            },
            {
                "PERCENT": ".393%"
            },
            {
                "GPE": "Tweet"
            }
        ]
    },
    [
        {
            "created_utc": 1575053275.0,
            "body": "Such rapid improvement",
            "score": 1509,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": 13.625951756495693,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.11127615244153219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575054719.0,
            "body": "Idk if anyone knows this but credit to Pascal and his work ethic for this one. Nick Nurse yesterday was on a Toronto sports radio show and he said the development for his shot started with assigning him with 450 shots after practice to develop his form and mechanics. Apparently, Pascal would go the extra mile and take 900 shots by the end of it all and it's paying off.",
            "score": 879,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Pascal"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Nick Nurse"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "yesterday"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Toronto"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "450"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Pascal"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 7.829142703339763,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575054533.0,
            "body": "Jesus Christ this dude got so good. \n\nKnew some shit was up when he shat all on the Warriors in G1 last year. \n\nMotherfucker got that Saiyan Improvement rate.",
            "score": 464,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Jesus Christ"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Knew"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "G1"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "last year"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Motherfucker"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Saiyan Improvement"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 4.0106097556259375,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.126331786908192
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575056925.0,
            "body": "Winning a championship for hard-working, young guys like Siakam and VanVleet can actually mean so much. It's like a validation that your hard work can pay off at the highest level, and with Kawhi leaving it gives them the motivation to not slack off and go at it again.",
            "score": 181,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 6.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam and VanVleet"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 1.4066463238114486,
            "sentiment_z-score": 1.1013625039213115
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575057962.0,
            "body": "pascal also couldn't hit a free throw or finish a lay up in his rookie year lol",
            "score": 151,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": 1.13060779747069,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.6063193281814219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575052662.0,
            "body": "Nurse is saying he has a year and a half to go before he becomes a legitimate shooter. He also added the caveat that Siakam improves so fast that   He could do it in half the time.",
            "score": 183,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "a year and a half"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "  "
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 1.425048892234166,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.11127615244153219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575052605.0,
            "body": "Harden-esque growth... He's gonna be a top 5 player in the future easily with his work ethic...",
            "score": 394,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "5"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 3.366519860830834,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.6063193281814219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575055107.0,
            "body": "He has great touch around the rim too.",
            "score": 41,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": 0.1184665342212422,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.35879774031147704
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575057979.0,
            "body": "Coachability is one of the best abilities to have as a player",
            "score": 43,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 5.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "one"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 0.13686910264395943,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.8538409160513667
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058118.0,
            "body": "I hope he continues to improve and spends most of if not his entire career in Toronto. He could easily become the franchises greatest player ever\n\nI like Kawhi, but it's hard to call someone a franchises greatest player when they were only there 1 season even if it did end with the team winning their first championship.",
            "score": 163,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 15.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Toronto"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "1 season"
                },
                {
                    "ORDINAL": "first"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 1.2410232080069936,
            "sentiment_z-score": 3.329056794750815
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058566.0,
            "body": "Someone make a Siakam subreddit",
            "score": 41,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 0.1184665342212422,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575054834.0,
            "body": "But don't worry, \"Caruso has had more surprising plays and noteworthy/improved play\"\n\n[https://twitter.com/DVSWhatItTweets/status/1200249492274061312](https://twitter.com/DVSWhatItTweets/status/1200249492274061312)",
            "score": 85,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Caruso"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 0.5233230395210213,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.6312886111683023
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575054181.0,
            "body": "Yeah but Ben Simmons shot one 3 against the Knicks so obviously he is the vastly superior player. Right guys? Guys?\n\nNow I’m sad.",
            "score": 107,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Ben Simmons"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "one 3"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Knicks"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 0.7257512921709109,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.13624543542841264
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575057575.0,
            "body": "Definitely unique and all the credits to him for the tremendous growth. As a Raptors fan, his debut seems to fit one of an athletic energy big man that could run the floor. There was definitely potential, but nothing too exciting.\n\nIn the last few years, he transitioned from making corner 3s to shooting anywhere outside at a respectable level. His play making and ball handling also improved which I think happens less with big men. \n\nWill be interested to see where he ends up peaking.",
            "score": 15,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 15.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "the last few years"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "3s"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.12076685527408186,
            "sentiment_z-score": 3.329056794750815
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575059108.0,
            "body": "Bill Simmons had him as the 7th best NBA player right now for good reason. He's not just a regular season guy either, I genuinely think he's an alpha dog now.\n\n#best player from Cameroon",
            "score": 30,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 9.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Bill Simmons"
                },
                {
                    "ORDINAL": "7th"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "NBA"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "#"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Cameroon"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 0.01725240789629741,
            "sentiment_z-score": 1.843927267531146
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575057907.0,
            "body": "Couldn’t imagine what it’s like having a player who can’t shoot practice through trial and error.",
            "score": 11,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.15757199211951634,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.6312886111683023
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058368.0,
            "body": "does american media even talk about siakam or anything toronto raptors related in general?",
            "score": 20,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "NORP": "american"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.07476043421728877,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575060082.0,
            "body": "Ironically, it's mirroring Kawhi's growth on offense. Although Kawhi did not have this good of a handle in year 4",
            "score": 8,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "year 4"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.18517584475359217,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.35879774031147704
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575061481.0,
            "body": "Siakam was such a atrocious shooter. In his 2nd year, he failed to make a 3 for a solid month. And it's not for trying, he attempted 25 shots or 1.7 attempts a game from the wide open corner in December of 2017. \n\nJust goes to show how hard he's worked.",
            "score": 7,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "his 2nd year"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "3"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "month"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "25"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "1.7"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "December of 2017"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.1943771289649508,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.3738533747781367
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058773.0,
            "body": "The only person similar is Giannis in recent memory. But he still never really developed a jump shot. Pascal is as monster",
            "score": 16,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Giannis"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Pascal"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.11156557106272323,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575059876.0,
            "body": "Honestly one of my favorite players outside of SA.",
            "score": 5,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "one"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "SA"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.21277969738766803,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.11127615244153219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575060108.0,
            "body": "Pretty sure this means teams just need to start recruiting random 6'9\" guys from Africa and hope they strike gold.",
            "score": 5,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "random 6'9"
                },
                {
                    "LOC": "Africa"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.21277969738766803,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.6063193281814219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575061257.0,
            "body": "If they could have kept Kawhi they might have won another 2 or 3...",
            "score": 10,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "2"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "3"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.16677327633087494,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.35879774031147704
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575057014.0,
            "body": "If he was a historically bad three point shooter. Now he’s taking pull up threes",
            "score": 4,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "three"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.22198098159902666,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.126331786908192
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058897.0,
            "body": "Danny Ainge passed on him three times",
            "score": 4,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Danny Ainge"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "three"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.22198098159902666,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575061714.0,
            "body": "Ok so nobody has mentioned him, but Danny Granger increased his ppg by 5 for 4 consecutive seasons. Not saying Danny is better than P, but he's the other guy I think of when it comes to the kind of improvement that Pascal has displayed.",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 5.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Danny Granger"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "5"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "4 consecutive seasons"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Danny"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Pascal"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.23118226581038526,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.8538409160513667
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575067996.0,
            "body": "Uh if ur gonna calculate percentages you gotta move the decimal point over. Right now ur saying he shoots <1% from 3 lol",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERCENT": "1%"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "3"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.23118226581038526,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.35879774031147704
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575068915.0,
            "body": "Work ethic > pure talent\n\nHope he stays with the Raptors. They deserve him. Don’t want anyone to get as burned as I felt when Kawhi left the Spurs after taking a similar trajectory",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 6.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "\n\nHope"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Spurs"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.23118226581038526,
            "sentiment_z-score": 1.1013625039213115
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575078527.0,
            "body": "You cursed him",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.23118226581038526,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575052579.0,
            "body": "[deleted]",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.24038355002174389,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575060934.0,
            "body": "And he's on the gd raptors. Love it. Lead us Spicy P!",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.24038355002174389,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.35879774031147704
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575062529.0,
            "body": "I didn't even know who he was two years ago.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "two years ago"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.24038355002174389,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575072424.0,
            "body": "I mean it is impressive don't get me wrong, but Brook Lopez literally transitioned from a face up post player who never took 3s last season to becoming a true stretch big in one year lol. Think it's more evident of the direction the league is moving if anything. Plenty of guys shoot 3s now, it's starting to become an expected skill no matter the position. \n\n&#x200B;\n\nLike props to Siakam for improving, but this is nothing new and we will continue to see players work on their 3 pt game.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 10.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Brook Lopez"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "3s"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "last season"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "one year"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "3s"
                },
                {
                    "MONEY": "x200B"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "3"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.24038355002174389,
            "sentiment_z-score": 2.091448855401091
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575078727.0,
            "body": "Did you jinx him??",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.24038355002174389,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575064931.0,
            "body": "For some reason I just keep thinking he's a better second option to kawhi than Paul George is. Paul George is better but I just feel like Pascal's game is built for the playoffs\n\nHe can operate out of the post  where as PG can't really. \n\nHe can score on different ways, he can shoot the three, take you on the post, finish at the rim. Not to mention, he's more efficient with his touches than Paul George. And he's not a bad defender. PG is better but siakam can hold his own.\n\nPG is more of a finesse guy and I worry if his shot isn't falling, what's he gonna do? He can drive to the basket but he doesn't do it as much as Pascal. He doesn't really post guys unless they're super small.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 5.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORDINAL": "second"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Paul George"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Paul George"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Pascal"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "three"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Paul George"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Pascal"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.24038355002174389,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.8538409160513667
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575055600.0,
            "body": "Yeah he's a top 10 player in the league \n\nRaptors gonna win the east and probably the whole thing again.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 7.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "10"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.24038355002174389,
            "sentiment_z-score": 1.3488840917912563
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058043.0,
            "body": "My Pistons could’ve drafted him but we went for Henry Ellenson 😅",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Henry Ellenson"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575060546.0,
            "body": "Someone talked (i believe some podcast) how much of it is that he started playing very late, at least compared to usual age, and that that's a big part why he is so smooth and simple and fast learning. Something about how kids a lot of the times learn bad shit when they are really young and it's hard to change (aka Lonzo shooting form ex) i believe Hakeem also started playing fairly late and he is probably the most skilled C of all time",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -7.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Lonzo"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Hakeem"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -2.116418138387971
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575061887.0,
            "body": "Love this dude.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.35879774031147704
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575062024.0,
            "body": "Spurs didn’t even bother to ask for him lol.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Spurs"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.13624543542841264
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575062950.0,
            "body": "Pretty good story. I’d be curious what his splits are against the better defensive teams. Celtics, Lakers, Clippers, etc. If he’s terrorizing those teams as well then he’s pretty full proof.\n\nWho did he hit the 5 3s against? Kind of lazy to check for the box lol.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 10.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Clippers"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "5"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 2.091448855401091
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575064184.0,
            "body": "Follows kawhi's trajectory actually. From can't shoot to one of the best in the league in a few short years.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "a few short years"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.11127615244153219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575064649.0,
            "body": "Just imagine his potential when you consider that Mark Embiid-Gasol is going to be around Siakam for a while. \n\nMight become a god-tier two way player",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Mark Embiid-Gasol"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "two"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.13624543542841264
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575065087.0,
            "body": "I remember 2 years ago when I said that if he could improve his 3 pt shooting to be around 35% then he could one day turn into a poor man's Draymond Green due to his improved ball-handing/passing/defense and I thought that was a huge compliment lol",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 8.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "2 years ago"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "3"
                },
                {
                    "PERCENT": "around 35%"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Draymond Green"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 1.5964056796612012
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575065313.0,
            "body": "The next Melo",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575065694.0,
            "body": "I love this guy cause we are from the same continent but hate him cause he killed my sixers. Can't hate the progression",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -6.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.8688965505180264
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575066228.0,
            "body": "reminds me of “brazilian kd” bruno cabloco. but if he was actually two years away from being two years away",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "two years"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "two years"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575067042.0,
            "body": "Breaking news young player gets better",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.11127615244153219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575067083.0,
            "body": "Raptors development system going over 1000",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575067150.0,
            "body": "Imagine winning MIP 2 years in a row... like WUT!!!\n\nEdit: WUUUUUUUUUTTTTTT!!!!",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 6.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "MIP 2 years"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "WUT"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 1.1013625039213115
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575067441.0,
            "body": "Pascal da Truth letting everyone know the Raps don't need Kawhi to DEFEND DIS CHIP.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Raps"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575067467.0,
            "body": "Reminder that if Casey remained head coach, he would never have allowed Siakam to develop into the offensive powerhouse that he is.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Casey"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.8788101990382471
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575068066.0,
            "body": "I still remember when I made a comment on Raptors reddit before the last time we got swept by the cavs. Saying how they should start spicy P over Ibaka and everyone shat on my comment . Great improvement by him tho, crazy how good he is now. Nick nurse played a role in it too, Casey barely played him when he was coach",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 6.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Ibaka"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Nick"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Casey"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 1.1013625039213115
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575068424.0,
            "body": "he reminds me of Giannis. Insane physically, improves every season.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Giannis"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Insane"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575068760.0,
            "body": "He gonna go sicko mode against Magic tonight.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Magic"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575070427.0,
            "body": "Mvp Lol naw",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Mvp Lol"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.35879774031147704
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575071339.0,
            "body": " He’s like Draymond Green but actually Good",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 5.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Draymond Green"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.8538409160513667
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575071848.0,
            "body": "Pascal \"Not Andrew Wiggins\" Siakam",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575074145.0,
            "body": "Raptors fan here. Feels amazing to be one of the teams with one of those hidden gem players, and honestly feeling like some of the other guys have so much left to grow as well. Masai is the fucking Goat GM. He's a god in Toronto right now",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 10.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "one"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Masai"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Goat GM"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Toronto"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 2.091448855401091
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575075143.0,
            "body": "Now THAT'S a spicy a-meatball.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575075859.0,
            "body": "Plenty of people develop their shot throughout their career.  But I have never seen someone develop it so quickly and significantly.  It's pretty insane.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.6312886111683023
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575076333.0,
            "body": "After his rookie year I thought Siakam would become a solid starter for the Raptors.\n\nI never ever could’ve expected something like this.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "his rookie year"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.6063193281814219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575076702.0,
            "body": "Meanwhile Ben Simmons is worse than when we drafted him",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Ben Simmons"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.126331786908192
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575079610.0,
            "body": "Mans gonna be the greatest Raptor of all time assuming he stays for a long time.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "NORP": "Mans"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.35879774031147704
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575069325.0,
            "body": "What is Ben Simmons excuse",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Ben Simmons"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.6312886111683023
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575052718.0,
            "body": "TIL",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "TIL"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575070447.0,
            "body": "Bad role player? You mean good role player that didn't have an outside shot.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575055902.0,
            "body": "Very impressive, but I think it's a stretch to call him MVP caliber.",
            "score": -7,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "MVP"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.32319510792397144,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.35879774031147704
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575052639.0,
            "body": "Cool what else? Did he also grow 4 inches over the offseason?",
            "score": -21,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "QUANTITY": "4 inches"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.4520130868829921,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.13624543542841264
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575054890.0,
            "body": "Don't curse him now",
            "score": -1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2679874026558197,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.6312886111683023
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575057541.0,
            "body": "Meh brook Lopez",
            "score": -1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Meh"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Lopez"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2679874026558197,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575063749.0,
            "body": "How open were those 3s tho?. Plus from what I've noticed, teams has not doubled him yet.",
            "score": -1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2679874026558197,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575062590.0,
            "body": "He’s honestly better than Lebron at this point.",
            "score": -7,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Lebron"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.32319510792397144,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.11127615244153219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575052901.0,
            "body": "Idk AD locked him down",
            "score": -24,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PRODUCT": "Idk AD"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.47961693951706796,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575053129.0,
            "body": "If he shoots 30% from above the break during the Sixers series, Kawhi stays in Toronto and they repeat as champs",
            "score": -36,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERCENT": "30%"
                },
                {
                    "EVENT": "the Sixers series"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Kawhi"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Toronto"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.5900323500533714,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058011.0,
            "body": "Such Raptor improvement",
            "score": 910,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": 8.114382513891881,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.11127615244153219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058497.0,
            "body": "Who else could be fighting for MIP this year against Siakam? It’d be insane to win that award two years in a row. Amazing.",
            "score": 110,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 7.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "MIP"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "this year"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "two years in a row"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 0.7533551448049868,
            "sentiment_z-score": 1.3488840917912563
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575064178.0,
            "body": "Well going from two years ago where most Raptors fans had nightmares over him being given the green light to being such a good shooter already is absolutely crazy.",
            "score": 6,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "two years ago"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Raptors"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.20357841317630943,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.13624543542841264
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058938.0,
            "body": "cant wait til he only shoots 3's next season",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "3's next season"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.23118226581038526,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575069582.0,
            "body": "Can’t believe I drafted Ben Simmons over Siakam in fantasy for my first pick",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Ben Simmons"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                },
                {
                    "ORDINAL": "first"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575070528.0,
            "body": "Dude might deserve b2b MIP tbh. Went from decent player to best role player in the league to certified allstar",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "b2b MIP"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.35879774031147704
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575071794.0,
            "body": "Offseason 🤙",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Offseason 🤙"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575073105.0,
            "body": "Reminds me of Kawhis development honestly",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575056226.0,
            "body": "I like the theory that his lack of basketball experience actually helped him as a shooter.\n\nMost guys make it to the NBA with bad habits which have already been committed to muscle memory by thousands and thousands of repetitions.  The reason guys like Ben Simmons and Lonzo Ball can't just \"fix\" their shot is that they've been practicing with bad form since they were kids.  \n\nSiakam arrived in the US as a blank slate- tall, athletic, hard-working and coachable.  It's way easier to teach good form than it is to fix bad form.",
            "score": 615,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "NBA"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "thousands and thousands"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Ben Simmons"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Lonzo Ball"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "US"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 5.400003671541088,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.3738533747781367
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575069363.0,
            "body": "Sounds kinda like Giannis. Some guys have sheer force of fucking will to take them to the top and their surroundings don't matter at all. Granted Siakam has probably had better coaches than Kidd but at the end of the day, you just almost never see guys make as much improvement as Siakam and Giannis have, and most of that is on the player as Nurse said.",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 6.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Giannis"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Granted Siakam"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Kidd"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "the end of the day"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Giannis"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Nurse"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.23118226581038526,
            "sentiment_z-score": 1.1013625039213115
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575073772.0,
            "body": "That’s some Larry bird shit",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Larry"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.3738533747781367
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575072214.0,
            "body": "if I could have people just rebound for me and pass it to me, I think I would shoot 900 shots on the regular. I understand they have a shit ton of other stuff to do, but for somebody who couldn’t make the elite levels, being assigned 450 shots a day sounds like a joke of a punishment",
            "score": 0,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "450"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.25878611844446114,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.6312886111683023
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575054971.0,
            "body": "I was never high on Siakam. I thought surely he'll struggle against Isaac. He owned him. I thought he'd struggle against Draymond. He didn't. That's when I knew he's a legit star.",
            "score": 190,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Isaac"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Draymond"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 1.489457881713676,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.3738533747781367
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575067063.0,
            "body": "Honestly, one of my favourite plays from the championship was that little side step he did at the end of game 6 to ice the game. It sounds silly but as soon has he got the ball I felt confident the Raps were going to win.",
            "score": 5,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 7.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "one"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "6"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Raps"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.21277969738766803,
            "sentiment_z-score": 1.3488840917912563
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575070915.0,
            "body": "Over 9000 on the Scoville scale.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "Over 9000"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Scoville"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575073685.0,
            "body": "Not just that, but it checks a box and frees them up to aim for a higher goal, winning the chip as the leader(s). Kinda like Kyrie wanting out from Bron's shadow (but Siakam and FVV don't have to leave to get their shot).",
            "score": 8,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 5.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Kinda"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Kyrie"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Bron"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.18517584475359217,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.8538409160513667
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575071657.0,
            "body": "The training wheels are off.",
            "score": 17,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.10236428685136462,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058902.0,
            "body": "I use to say, hell be another Patrick Patterson. But his ceiling is Draymond green... His rookie year",
            "score": 79,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Patrick Patterson"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Draymond"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 0.46811533425286966,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.3738533747781367
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575056670.0,
            "body": "By playoffs he’ll be pulling up from the logo",
            "score": 99,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": 0.652141018480042,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575056250.0,
            "body": "Jesus, he'll be a legit shooter by the playoffs then.",
            "score": 25,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Jesus"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.02875401316049568,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.13624543542841264
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575063564.0,
            "body": "Siakam training as 1000 shadow clones. Cutting his training time into mere seconds.",
            "score": 6,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "1000"
                },
                {
                    "TIME": "mere seconds"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.20357841317630943,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.6312886111683023
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575074307.0,
            "body": "Im late to the party, anyone mention he only started playing 9 years ago?",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "9 years ago"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.24038355002174389,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575052648.0,
            "body": "Simmons already has him at 7th. Even I don't have him ranked that high lol",
            "score": 261,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORDINAL": "7th"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 2.142749060720138,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.35879774031147704
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575059198.0,
            "body": "I agree. Siakam is gonna be a monster in the future. He already is, but he's gonna be insane.",
            "score": 11,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.15757199211951634,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.6312886111683023
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575061863.0,
            "body": "He can be a top 5 player but I dont know if he will easily be one. That's really difficult.",
            "score": 7,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "5"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.1943771289649508,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.13624543542841264
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575053363.0,
            "body": "I wouldn’t call it hardenesque at all. Harden in his last year in OKC was already a top 20 player in the league. He just didn’t have the opportunity.",
            "score": 21,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "his last year"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "OKC"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "20"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.06555915000593016,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.6063193281814219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575064277.0,
            "body": "That's right. His midrange shot is not there yet but he has been experimenting this season.",
            "score": 12,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "this season"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.1483707079081577,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575065181.0,
            "body": "Pascal The Redeemer",
            "score": 50,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": 0.20127809212346975,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575065659.0,
            "body": "I say Lowry for the Raptors, years as their best player and was a big part of the championship. Siakam can get there though",
            "score": 49,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Lowry"
                },
                {
                    "LOC": "Raptors"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": ", years"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 0.19207680791211115,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.6063193281814219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575070375.0,
            "body": "I don't think he's ever leaving Toronto. Pascal is like the living embodiment of everything Masai is trying to accomplish with Giants of Africa and the culture he's trying to establish for the Toronto Raptors, he's gonna do everything to retain him. He's gonna be our Kobe/Dirk/Duncan (I mean that in a loyalty sense, not all time greatness sense, but who knows? :P )",
            "score": 7,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 10.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Toronto"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Pascal"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Masai"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Giants of Africa"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "the Toronto Raptors"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Kobe"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Dirk"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Duncan"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.1943771289649508,
            "sentiment_z-score": 2.091448855401091
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575065145.0,
            "body": "/r/torontoraptors",
            "score": 100,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": 0.6613423026914006,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575057320.0,
            "body": ">Siakim \n\nMY EYES!!!",
            "score": 32,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Siakim"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 0.035654976319014646,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058289.0,
            "body": "That guy is so dumb it boils my blood, he's really arguing that Caruso has had more highlight plays this season over Siakam.",
            "score": 23,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Caruso"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "season"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.04715658158321291,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.6312886111683023
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058360.0,
            "body": "Embarrassing.",
            "score": 11,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.15757199211951634,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.8788101990382471
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575068545.0,
            "body": "That’s the worst take I’ve ever seen in my life.",
            "score": 5,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.21277969738766803,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.126331786908192
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575057493.0,
            "body": "Can't even spell his name.",
            "score": 8,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.18517584475359217,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575064867.0,
            "body": "People have to stop smoking crack on the job. This take is atrocious.",
            "score": 4,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.22198098159902666,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.3738533747781367
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575073480.0,
            "body": "Give that clown some makeup and a storm drain to hide in",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.24038355002174389,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.6312886111683023
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575073758.0,
            "body": "Caruso is pretty legit like a young Iguodala I love that bald boi",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 6.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Caruso"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Iguodala"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.24038355002174389,
            "sentiment_z-score": 1.1013625039213115
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575070772.0,
            "body": "Our fans are so fucking sensitive lol",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.6312886111683023
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575055438.0,
            "body": "Simmons is shooting 50% from 3 this season. How do you even guard someone like that?",
            "score": 102,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERCENT": "50%"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "3 this season"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 0.6797448711141179,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.11127615244153219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575055427.0,
            "body": "Smart and Siakam should inspire Simmons but he seems to just not want to be able to shoot so idk what the hell his deal is.",
            "score": 26,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.019552728949137062,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.6312886111683023
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575056721.0,
            "body": "Maybe this is his 1 3pt season, then he’ll make 29 next year, then make 2.5/game at 39% in 2 years....\n\n^^we ^^can ^^hope",
            "score": 17,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "1 3pt season"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "29"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "next year"
                },
                {
                    "PERCENT": "39%"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "2 years"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.10236428685136462,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.11127615244153219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575060723.0,
            "body": "His form wasnt even that bad on that shot. Idk why he doesnt shoot more to at least attempt to expand his game https://streamable.com/132ey",
            "score": 9,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.17597456054223357,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.126331786908192
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575055944.0,
            "body": "Now that I think of it it's kinda fucked up that the Sixers had to be historically bad for like 4 years just to get that's 2016 1st overall pick and select Simmons, meanwhile Toronto was cashing in that playoff revenue while Masai causally snagged the best player in the draft at 27",
            "score": 34,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -4.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "DATE": "like 4 years"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "2016 1st"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Simmons"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "Toronto"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Masai"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "27"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 0.054057544741731876,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.3738533747781367
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575067543.0,
            "body": "Bruh we picked Furkan Korkmaz over him 😫🔫",
            "score": 0,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Bruh"
                },
                {
                    "LOC": "Furkan Korkmaz"
                },
                {
                    "GPE": "🔫"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.25878611844446114,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575062954.0,
            "body": ">best player from Cameroon\n\n*sad airplane noises*",
            "score": 24,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.037955297371854296,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.13624543542841264
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575065589.0,
            "body": "Who cares man, fkin espn",
            "score": 6,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.20357841317630943,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.11127615244153219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575071152.0,
            "body": "I remember him in that last series vs the Cavs when he was still bench mob.  He was getting wide open looks from Kyle and DeMar and bricking almost all of them.  By mid way through that series they didn't even guard him out there and he was passing open shots to drive into a packed paint waiting for him.  It was like the team was playing 4v5 on offense.  He was still an important part of that team because of his defensive energy, but he really held the team back on offense. Now he leads them on both sides while Kyle's been out.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Kyle"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "DeMar"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "mid"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "4v5"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Kyle"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575069848.0,
            "body": "Or 4 or 5...",
            "score": -2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "4 or 5"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.27718868686717835,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575052647.0,
            "body": "Man get the fuck out of here with that shit.\n\nYes, unique means one of a kind but it’s used in our current language to describe something that’s rare as well.",
            "score": 9,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -5.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "one"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.17597456054223357,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.6213749626480816
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575075397.0,
            "body": "> Brook Lopez literally transitioned from a face up post player who never took 3s last season to becoming a true stretch big in one year lol. \n\nHe started shooting 3s on the Nets and then shot some on the Lakers as well. Before that he was already a very good shooter of long 2s and FTs.\n\nAnd taking set shots, is different then what Siakam is doing now of the dribble.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 9.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Brook Lopez"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "3s"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "last season"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "one year"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "3s"
                },
                {
                    "FAC": "Nets"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Lakers"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 1.843927267531146
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575065751.0,
            "body": "Being compared to Paul George is pretty damn incredible - PG is definitely one of the top 5 players in the league when healthy\n\nPG was getting MVP considerations last year before injuries",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Paul George"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "5"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "\n\nPG"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "MVP"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "last year"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.24038355002174389,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.13624543542841264
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575057404.0,
            "body": "I think you have had a little bit too much of daddy's eggnog",
            "score": 14,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.12996813948544048,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575063350.0,
            "body": "Who?",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.23118226581038526,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575073374.0,
            "body": "If it's any consolation, at the time we drafted him a lot of Raptors fans were mad that we skipped on Skal Labissiere on a *literally who.*",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Skal Labissiere"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.126331786908192
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575065293.0,
            "body": "They definitely asked for either Siakam or OG but Raptors didn't budge.....a lot of Raptors fans were expecting Siakam or OG to be involved in the trade, but thankfully Masai is in charge.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam or OG but Raptors"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam or OG"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Masai"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575069637.0,
            "body": "The lolknicks",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575075475.0,
            "body": "I second this question",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORDINAL": "second"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575071571.0,
            "body": "Nah I mean bad role player. He had no shot, had no moves to finish inside so his scoring came from almost purely fastbreak dunks. His defense was also not that good, he had high motor was athletic and long but he got cooked a lot and he fouled a lot",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.24038355002174389,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.8788101990382471
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058435.0,
            "body": "26/8.5/4 on 48/39/82 splits , great defense on a winning team without its second best player is MVP caliber.",
            "score": 9,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 10.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "26/8.5/4"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "48/39/82"
                },
                {
                    "ORDINAL": "second"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "MVP"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.17597456054223357,
            "sentiment_z-score": 2.091448855401091
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575056986.0,
            "body": "man I swear, I see you commenting on like every post. Most of your comments are reasonable, but some of your comments just sound salty and hateful",
            "score": 6,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.20357841317630943,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575052688.0,
            "body": "Also, wanted to note that Karl Malone is a bitch.",
            "score": 20,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -5.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Karl Malone"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.07476043421728877,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.6213749626480816
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575052715.0,
            "body": "[deleted]",
            "score": 4,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.22198098159902666,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575056833.0,
            "body": "thanks for the comment",
            "score": 4,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.22198098159902666,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.11127615244153219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575065348.0,
            "body": "Teams have absolutely been doubling him",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.23118226581038526,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575062911.0,
            "body": "Lol chill",
            "score": 8,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Lol"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.18517584475359217,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.35879774031147704
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575065808.0,
            "body": "Lol",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Lol"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.35879774031147704
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575053198.0,
            "body": "We locked down Lebron even more that game, guess he sucks too.",
            "score": 28,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Lebron"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.0011501605264198271,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.126331786908192
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575053747.0,
            "body": "Smart players look for ways to avoid that situation and he did, so uh\n\nYeah not everyone can just bully their way past monoliths like AD the way Giannis can",
            "score": 10,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Giannis"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.16677327633087494,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.13624543542841264
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575053484.0,
            "body": "There was literally zero chance kawhi would stay in toronto even if that did happen",
            "score": 32,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "zero"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 0.035654976319014646,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.11127615244153219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575054080.0,
            "body": "Kawhi was never going to stay.  He didn’t want to be there regardless of what happened",
            "score": 11,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Kawhi"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.15757199211951634,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.13624543542841264
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575062974.0,
            "body": "It really is the best time to be a Raptor fan, with half our young players breaking out at the same time lol. FVV,  Siakam, OG, Davis ..",
            "score": 510,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 9.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "half"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": " Siakam, OG"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Davis"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 4.433868829348434,
            "sentiment_z-score": 1.843927267531146
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575076009.0,
            "body": "Velociraptor",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058890.0,
            "body": "Wiggins maybe",
            "score": 124,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": 0.8821731237640075,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058865.0,
            "body": "I think Brandon Ingran is the non-Siakam front runner, while Jaylen Brown and Damontas Sabonis also are contenders.",
            "score": 135,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Brandon Ingran"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Jaylen Brown"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 0.9833872500889522,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575060249.0,
            "body": "Devonte Graham went from fringe NBA player averaging 4.7 pts and 2.6 assists to a borderline All-Star who is averaging 18ppg and 7.5 assists on 33 minutes.",
            "score": 85,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Devonte Graham"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "NBA"
                },
                {
                    "QUANTITY": "4.7 pts and"
                },
                {
                    "QUANTITY": "2.6 assists"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "18ppg"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "7.5"
                },
                {
                    "TIME": "33 minutes"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 0.5233230395210213,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575063533.0,
            "body": "FVV 👀",
            "score": 4,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.22198098159902666,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575058871.0,
            "body": "The improvement isn't by leaps and bounds, but Luka has definitely taken his game to the next level, as well.",
            "score": 18,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Luka"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.093163002640006,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.11127615244153219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575065693.0,
            "body": "Ingram?",
            "score": 5,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.21277969738766803,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575067746.0,
            "body": "I’m biased but Bam Adebayo has a case",
            "score": 4,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -2.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Bam Adebayo"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.22198098159902666,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.8788101990382471
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575062924.0,
            "body": "Jaylen Brown",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Jaylen Brown"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.23118226581038526,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575066922.0,
            "body": "I sincerely think that if Fred VanVleet maintains good currently pace (we'll see what happens when Lowry returns) that he has a pretty great chance as well.",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 11.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Fred VanVleet"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Lowry"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.23118226581038526,
            "sentiment_z-score": 2.3389704432710356
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575068203.0,
            "body": "Fultz",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575068363.0,
            "body": "Ingram and Doncic and they're both easily frontrunners over Siakam. Could throw FVV in the mix if you wanted, but the first two are the real deal.",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                },
                {
                    "ORDINAL": "first"
                },
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "two"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575068390.0,
            "body": "OG and Fred VanVleet",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Fred VanVleet"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575069176.0,
            "body": "Shai I think has a really good chance",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 5.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Shai"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.8538409160513667
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575071915.0,
            "body": "Graham or Doncic?",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Graham"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Doncic"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575074730.0,
            "body": "Brogdon for me",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "GPE": "Brogdon"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575075418.0,
            "body": "> Who else could be fighting for MIP this year against Siakam?\n\nSiakam won MIP last year, can a player even do that twice in a row?",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "MIP"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "this year"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                },
                {
                    "ORG": "MIP"
                },
                {
                    "DATE": "last year"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.13624543542841264
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575076865.0,
            "body": "Lamar Jackson",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Lamar Jackson"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575062623.0,
            "body": "He's going to start taking his free throws from the three point line.",
            "score": 3,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 1.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "CARDINAL": "three"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.23118226581038526,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.13624543542841264
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575056742.0,
            "body": "He also started off as a soccer player, and quite a good one from what I understand, which is why he has such deadly quick footwork.\n\nBut yes it certainly also helped that he didn’t have terribly ingrained bad habits coming into the league.",
            "score": 330,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": -5.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": 2.7776376713038826,
            "sentiment_z-score": -1.6213749626480816
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575057456.0,
            "body": "Tom Brady actually started playing football when he was in high school too and I think Steve Nash was a soccer player until he was older as well.",
            "score": 39,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Tom Brady"
                },
                {
                    "PERSON": "Steve Nash"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": 0.10006396579852496,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575068516.0,
            "body": "Siakam brand magical putty ready to be formed into your favourite super star.",
            "score": 6,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 5.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORG": "Siakam"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.20357841317630943,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.8538409160513667
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575071824.0,
            "body": "So the trick to being good at basketball is to first be bad at basketball.  Got it.",
            "score": 2,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "ORDINAL": "first"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.24038355002174389,
            "sentiment_z-score": -0.3837670232983575
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575070074.0,
            "body": "This theory is actually really interesting. I fully believe it to be true, but is there any science to back this up?",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 4.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.6063193281814219
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575070347.0,
            "body": "I had not heard this, but that also makes sense.  Nurse has talked about having to get guys to buy in to reworking their entire mechanics, but if you have none to start you only learn good habits",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [
                {
                    "PERSON": "Nurse"
                }
            ],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.35879774031147704
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575073168.0,
            "body": "Very good point.  👍",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 3.0,
            "entities": [],
            "score_z-score": -0.2495848342331025,
            "sentiment_z-score": 0.35879774031147704
        },
        {
            "created_utc": 1575077173.0,
            "body": "You might be on to something there",
            "score": 1,
            "distinguished": null,
            "sentiment": 0.0,
